Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, and so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonder.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us.
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Saru, why are you standing like that?
If I'm going to be a
statue, I prefer this pose.
This is no time to be playing around.
Do you think you could at least
do something about all this blood?
I'm getting nauseous just looking at it.
So quit looking at it then.
It's kind of hard to ignore.
Do you still think it
was a bright idea to cut
your own legs off so that
we can escape from here?
That wasn't the point.
I was going to cut them
off so that we could fight.
Oh, was that the plan?
Because that's an even worse idea.
Whatever.
Seriously, sometimes I think you were
born without any common sense at all.
We're stuck.
You're about to be turned into wax
statues and the two of them are bickering.
You really don't seem to understand
the danger of the situation at all.
Hey, short guy, is that all
the fight you got left in ya?
Yeah, I think I'm gonna have to let
someone else take over from here.
They don't seem terribly worried about
what's going to happen to them, Mr. Three.
And you don't seem terribly worried about
making sure it happens, Miss Golden Week.
Solidify already.
If you want to die in a cool
pose, Nami, you better hurry up.
Mr.
Bushido, could you please take
this a little more seriously?
Hey, your pose could
use a little work, too.
Shut up about the posing already!
They're acting so careless like this
for no other reason than to mock us.
This is very annoying.
All right.
though he doesn't seem to be a
very reliable man if you ask me mr.
three Hmm we'll be happy
to take care of the
Straw Hat pissed take
care of him please Don't
be ridiculous I sent
you to take care of him
once already and look he's
Standing in front of us
alive and well interfering
with my artistic
process I Think it's clear
that you can't handle
him he's obviously too
much for you Wouldn't you
agree you two can deal
with the others if you?
You think you're up to it, that is.
I'll take care of him.
I think a Straw Hat Luffy statue would make
an excellent addition to my collection.
I think I've had way
more than enough of you.
And if you cretins know what's
good for you, you'll give up now.
Kay, we're safely in position now.
We got your back from here, Luffy.
Hmm?
Did you say something?
Now I've got you. CASTLES!
What's he doing?
Loopy!
Damn, I got caught already. Moron!
Hmm, what is this thing?
Whatever it is, it's nice and heavy.
Almost too simple.
All right, just once more.
Hmm.
Yeah, this should be perfect.
Candle lock!
Whoa!
Hey, giant guys!
Excuse me!
Uh, what the?
What is his widow doing now?
Huh?
Tom, Tom!
All right!
We'll be there!
Hey, the thing on my legs
broke at the same time!
Um, but wait, why are they still there?
We're okay now.
We didn't die.
We're still alive, but that
really didn't help at all.
That was a close one, but
why didn't you guys run away?
Because we're stuck
here, isn't that obvious?
Oh, really?
So that's what's going on?
The only thing you guys kept saying
was that I needed to break the pillar.
Mr.
Bushido, do you really think it's a good
idea to put our lives in that guy's hands?
Well, we don't exactly have
much of a choice, do we?
I don't know about you, but I'm having a
little bit of trouble moving right now.
I can't move. What's happening? My body.
I don't know.
No, it won't move, I can't move at all.
You fools, all you did was
move the candles closer.
And by doing so, you only sped
up the solidified process.
You'll become wax figures even sooner now.
Well done.
That guy, I want to punch him
right in his smug little face.
Wait, you guys are gonna
turn into Wax figures?
That's what we've been trying to tell you!
Please just hurry up and
destroy this thing, Luffy!
Right, yeah, I'm on it!
I don't think so, Straw Hat.
Now get out of my way!
Wax, wax, harpoon!
Exploding Star!
That's not very flavorful your gunpowder
must not be too good
there's no way he ate it?
This isn't really looking good for us
ladies this damn thing is speeding up!
Good thing I've Got my pose ready. Moron!
Come on, Murphy!
You have to hurry!
Right, so the pumpkin thing has to go!
I'm on it now!
It's no use!
Candle wars!
Bazooka!
Hey, out of my way!
I was just thinking the same thing.
I would greatly appreciate it if you would
quit interfering with
my creative activities.
Candle, look!
I got a mallet!
Huh?
Gum-Gum!
No, you don't! Candle, look!
Mr. Three!
No way.
Luffy!
Hurry up and break this
thing before we die up here!
Um, no.
Quit joking around and hurry!
Nuh-uh.
Quit being an idiot!
Now's not really a good time! Luffy!
Please just do it! Not now. I...
just don't feel like saving you.
Luffy, what's wrong?
My color's trapped.
Hey, Luffy, there's no
time to space out now.
Do something about this already.
Yeah, I know.
Then quit just standing there, will you?
Come on, Luffy.
I know what I should do,
but I don't feel like it.
Dammit, why do you keep saying that?
We're about to be turned into wax statues.
Do you understand me?
We're going to die yeah
but for some reason i
can't get motivated to
help what do you mean?
Can't get motivated
what's going on here what
is wrong with him our
friends are going to die?
If he doesn't do something to help them
soon i'll snap him out
of it let's go Karoo
Where did you two come from?
Just give up.
Your friend has already
fallen into a nasty trap.
That's right.
Haven't you noticed what he's standing on?
Standing?
Let me take a look.
What's that?
There's a strange black
pattern on the ground.
I don't get it.
What's so important about that thing?
Yeah, you're right.
You really don't get it at all, do you?
That's funny.
Paint.
That's what's funny.
It's just paint.
You and your friends don't
stand a chance of escaping now.
Conney!
Let's make a run for it!
Oh, great, now they're running away.
Let's get them.
Full speed ahead, Karoo!
Hey, wait, I'm not on yet!
Slow down, Karoo! Let me on!
Hey, bird, you hear me?
Let me on!
Just let me on! No!
Why are you afraid of me?
I thought you were a duck, not a chicken!
Slow down, will you?
Please, Karoo!
Miss Golden Week's responsible.
I know that this is your doing!
It's my colors trap, Betrayal Black.
If you touch the paint, you'll
want to betray your friends,
no matter what they might say
even if they beg and plead for
help what's she talking about i
don't understand what's going on
here she's a painter she uses
her paint to create different
emotions each color is a feeling
her sense of color is so complete
she can manipulate your mind just
a splash of one of her colors
and you'll be under her control
under her control well that's
not good that simple-minded oaf
is already too easy to control
the last thing we need is someone
I'm messing with his mind.
Does that mean that all he needs to do is
get away from the paint and he'll be okay?
Luffy, move away from
there, quickly! No, don't!
Luffy, listen!
Whatever you do, please don't step
outside the black circle, all right?
I'm begging!
What are you saying?
We don't want you to save us, Luffy.
Please stay away from us.
No way.
I get it now.
We just needed to say the exact
opposite of what we wanted him to do.
Oh hey what?
What just happened?
That was acting really strange.
Okay I'm on my way. Right?
Never mind, I just want
to laugh right now.
Wave!
Moron!
What now?
Colors trap again, laughter yellow.
You should not have
stepped out of the circle.
Now it's on his clothing.
Luffy, quick, take off your shirt!
I'd love to, really.
But right now I'm too busy laughing.
It's getting bad.
If the wax keeps falling at this rate!
We'll be lucky to stay
alive for five minutes.
Can you guys come here just to play tag?
Look!
When Usopp ran into Luffy the Pink Smudge!
Jeez, what's going on?
I felt all weird again.
Hey, painter girl!
Would you stop messing with me already?
But you were having such a good time.
Wasn't it funny?
Well, yeah, it was kind
of funny, but stop!
I've got to see about
breaking that pumpkin now!
Gom, gom!
Another color strap!
Time for Bullfight Red!
Bazooka!
What were you aiming at?
I just can't let you break it.
Mr.
Three wouldn't be happy about that at all.
What'd you do?
During a bullfight, a bull can't
control his urge to attack the red cape.
Likewise, you can't do anything
now but attack that red circle.
That's what I did.
Okay, that does it!
I'm mad now!
Come, come, I'm losing!
Having fun.
Aw. Oh, great.
At this rate, he's never
gonna be able to beat her.
Now all of his strength is useless.
Now to finish up, we'll mix the laughter
yellow on your back with some Sadness Blue.
The last color's trap, tranquil green.
Ugh, that's some good tea.
Wolf!
So, what happens now?
See, I told you you should've posed,
but you wouldn't listen to
me, and now it's too late.
You're gonna die like that.
Are you really still talking about that?
Damn, how can they just
keep running like that?
Nose fancy, double camera!
You missed us, jerk!
Way to go, Karoo!
My turn now special attack let's start.
We need to get back to
Luffy and the others now.
Chasing them around isn't
getting us anywhere I noticed.
I hate to use this on
useless pests like them
but it looks like we may
not have a choice now.
This little beauty should be quite handy.
A .44 caliber, six-shot
flintlocked revolver.
It's a new model out of the South Blue.
Continuous fire.
And when I shoot it, the
bullets are invisible.
When Luffy was acting
so strange back there,
those two agents mentioned
something about paint.
The paint must have something
to do with Luffy's behavior.
There was also some yellow paint on his
back when we crashed into him earlier.
That's got to be the key.
We just have to do something about
the paint before it's too late.
Hurry!
This really is some nice tea.
Luffy! Hey! Wake up!
It's nice tea, it's so nice.
Very nice.
Why are you sitting
there and drinking tea?
Run all you want, it's all
over for you and your friends.
Here comes my best trick so far.
Special Attack Exploding Starbler!
Aaaaaaahhhhhh!
What an idiot!
He missed the target and
hit his friend instead!
Good, that was the last of his bullets!
Breeze, breath, ball!
Did I forget to mention that
my breath is also explosive?
Damn, I can't believe this guy.
He didn't have any bullets to begin with.
Hey, Karoo, are you alright?
Luffy, you snap out of it yet?
Yeah, I'm good now. Thanks.
So he didn't miss.
His plan this whole time was to burn the
collar trap on the Straw Hat's shirt.
I'm tired of your stupid paints.
You're through.
I'm not going to let you
hurt any more of my friends!
Now I'm really mad!
This is getting weird.
It's been a long time,
and no one's come back.
I wonder what's going on.
This island's crazy.
Anything could have happened
to Nami, Vivi, and the others,
which means that cooking this
lizard may have to wait for a while.
Hey, Nami!
Vivi! Vivi!
Can you hear me?
Hey, beautiful ladies!
If you can hear me,
please just say something!
That's strange.
What's this?
Oh, you're mad, are you?
Look at your friends.
Being mad won't do them any good.
Oh, yes it will!
They're still alive!
Are they now?
Look again.
All they need is some
Miss Golden Weeks paint
and there'll be perfect
wax statues Face it.
You're too late to save them.
They're gone, and you know it
Mr.
Fight is right about that Your
fritz are finished because
you are too late to help them
and now it's your turn to die
It's time for...
Candy!
Champion! Yeah!
What the heck is that? That thing,
that is what he used one time to take down
someone with a 42 million barrier bounty.
That's Mr.
Three's most dangerous work of art.
Time to use your talents,
Miss Golden Week.
I need an extra special
paint job for my armor.
And don't forget to be artistic.
After that, can I take a break?
Why yes, you can go get some tea.
I'd prefer it if you stayed
out of this actually.
When I'm in this armor, I'm
utterly impervious to harm.
This suit is as hard as iron.
It may be made of wax,
but it fits like a glove,
and it's impossible for anyone to pierce.
And you don't stand a chance against it.
This artwork is flawless!
Wow, that's so cool!
Why are you admiring him?
Fight!
Just a little more laughter yellow.
Right! Gah! Gah!
Heat job complete!
And now... Gah!
Champion bite!
Harvest field maneuver!
Gah!
Nice try!
Not good!
Luffy's attacks don't work
against that guy's armor!
The wax is choking me!
Wax!
Of course!
Why didn't I realize it before now?
It's all wax, which means
that it must be able to melt!
Luffy, we need to use fire.
No matter how hard it
is, wax is still wax.
The others only hardened
a few moments ago.
We should still be able to save them.
No way, seriously?
Yeah, that's correct.
You idiot, don't tell them that!
But it doesn't really matter
if you realize that now.
You have no hope of saving them.
They have 30 seconds left at most.
After that, their hearts
will slow to a stop.
As we speak, their
writhing in silent pain.
Barely conscious, they're hanging
onto their lives by a thread,
terrified of their impending
doom and unable to move or even
speak for help and they know that
you are too late to save them.
I'll save them right now.
I don't need 30 seconds.
Freeze, breath, pull!
Who's up now?
When we say you don't stand a
chance, it's best to believe us.
Damn it, we're running out of time!
Just give up.
Listen, I need you to grab
hold of this rope, Karoo.
Well, this looks like a potty.
Now, what are you two planning?
Do you think I could join in on the fun?
Karoo, run now.
Get going!
Just run around all the candlesticks
and move as quick as you can!
Come on, I don't know why you bother.
Excuse me. Oh, jeez.
Can you handle my crescendo stone?
I wonder just how many kilograms
you will be able to endure.
Ten kilograms.
One hundred kilograms.
Two hundred kilograms.
Three hundred kilograms.
Damn it!
Hold still, you cracker!
Give it up!
No use!
Your brains are a permanent
part of my collection now!
Accept it!
They're not!
There's no way I'm gonna let
you have my friends, candle boy!
I don't have any fire, so I'm
gonna have to roar at yours!
I hope that's okay!
That hurts, grip pulling!
Stop it! Hold on!
That tiny little flame isn't
gonna work quickly enough!
The rope that Karoo has,
light that on fire! A rope?
How's that supposed to help us?
Trust me on this, I covered
the whole thing in oil.
It'll be hot, but it's the only
way and they should be all right!
Uh, whoops.
Hope the others don't get all burned up.
Curse you, you stupid straw-haired pirate!
You destroyed my precious candle set!
How dare you show such disregard
for autistic integrity!
You'll pay for this!
No!
You're not getting away with that!
Damn it!
How dare you mock Baroque works, agents!
I'm sick and tired of
you and your friends.
Got that?
Okay, playtime is really over now.
I'm going to break that scrawny little
neck of yours into a million paces.
Ten thousand kilogram dancing!
That was really hot.
Couldn't you have thought up another plan?
You're being a little picky
here, don't you think?
Aren't you at least a little bit grateful?
You have a point there.
Thanks.
It's amazing.
I can't believe we're actually alive.
Got out of the wax, did you?
Well, I've had enough.
We simply cannot afford for you
to screw up our mission anymore.
Hey, Mr. Five!
Special attack!
Exploding Star!
You fool!
Haven't you figured out that
your pathetic explosives?
Don't affect me at all they're nothing
to an exploding man you took the bait!
I'm sorry i just told a
little lie that wasn't
an exploding star that was
a special tabasco star!
I had to learn how effective
that thing was the hard way!
Damn you stupid parrot!
Time for a full-body explosion!
There'll be nothing left of you!
Ow!
Oh, let go of me!
I'm sorry!
Please let go! Let him go!
I'm too young to die!
Flaming, holding, getting!
You know, these flaming
swords aren't too bad.
Zoro!
Hey there, glad to see
you made it out alive.
Heh, yeah.
Master?
So now it seems two foes are left.
Bird guy, let's go!
Ah!
Real men don't interfere
with someone else's fight!
So good of you to come!
I've been expecting you.
Welcome to my Wax Wax Manor!
What's going on?
Why, just a little game of hide and seek.
Can you figure out which one is me?
I'd say it appears you picked the
wrong group of people to go up against.
You're no match for my intellectual
prowess and artistic abilities.
You're just another buffoon
who acts on blind instinct
and uses brute force to
solve all his problems.
You can't hope to catch an
intellectual giant like me!
I am a Baroque Works agent.
Every assignment that is given
to me I see through to its end.
So if you think you're ready,
then just step forward.
That's right, just take a little step.
And as soon as your back is
turned, I'm going to stab you.
Right through that pathetically
noble little heart of yours.
Come, come!
How could you have known
that this is where I was?
Instinct.
Ah!
Hold on, what am I doing?
I shouldn't be sitting here all relaxed,
just casually sipping tea without
a single care in the world.
Nami, Vivi,
and the others could be waiting out there
right now for me to come and help them.
I am still curious
about one thing, though.
What is a nice, relaxing place like this
doing smack in the middle of an ancient,
creepy jungle?
Huh?
What?
A transponder snail.
Yeah, hello.
You've reached the crap cafe.
Can I take your order?
You can quit fooling around now, jackass.
Now then, your report's a little
bit late, don't you think?
Huh?
My report, you say?
And to whom exactly am I speaking, please?
Me, Mr. Zero.
There is a treasure I better be found.
The odds that you'll find
it will slip to none!
The world's such a big
place, the oceans are wide.
Don't look at home,
won't help you find it.
Just give up your time, spend on the call.
Even so.
If someone tries to keep
us from moving home,
The factor behind our
backs just keeps us strong.
It's too bad cause we're
still selling for it.
So fun for ya, just leave us alone?
It may be foolish,
chasing impossible things.
But I've just gotta try!
The crazier the dream, the
more ambition I've gotta need.
It may be for this drive and home.
But I know that I've just gotta buy.
The farther the sea, the greater paradise.
We've gotta find!
Don't be about just people trying.
And you see that you've loved you too.
The horizon of your dreams?